{
    "id": "fd152bcc8e64490da9d5d1c552e1f24c",
    "title": "Present continuous tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "04ba4c8c54f74cd3aadfa688bb8610ed",
            "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Jane …………………. in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "works",
                        "is working",
                        "are working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. Oliver Twist at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is reading",
                        "am reading",
                        "are reading"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………… TV.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is watching",
                        "am watching",
                        "are watching"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who ……………….. the violin?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is playing",
                        "are playing",
                        "am playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t make noise. The baby …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is sleeping",
                        "are sleeping",
                        "am sleeping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… in the park now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is waiting",
                        "am waiting",
                        "are waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jane and Susie ………………… in the kitchen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is cooking",
                        "are cooking",
                        "am cooking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………… pizza at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is making",
                        "are making",
                        "am making"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mother ………………….. a sweater.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is knitting",
                        "are knitting",
                        "am knitting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susan and her friend …………………. over for lunch.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is coming",
                        "are coming",
                        "am coming"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}